[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Is this about the base?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I think the first presidential debate is the biggest night of Mitt Romney's political life now because the Democrats did not stumble here.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "They're going to be crucial, aren't they?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "But actually, that is not even a joke.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "He fact checks himself, right?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "He would very much like that, and if you would help him do that, he'd also repeal any other amendment so that you could be his vice president, Piers.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "And if you can't have him, can we have him in Britain to be prime minister?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Oh, she actually came backstage and just said, Awesome.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "What did she say when you got backstage?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "She was emotional and excited and actually really fired up.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Was she emotional?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "There's several things, and I see it first through the eyes of someone in the energy sector.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "From a business point of view, have you heard anything here that makes you feel infused, encouraged for the future of business under Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I'm not sure I see weakness.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "To guarantee victory, where do you still see a bit of weakness that you have to tighten up on?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I think you have to continue to see an increase in the jobs produced in the private sector.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What would be good news for Barack Obama, and what would be a warning sign?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, when Romney talked about 12 million jobs, he never laid out a plan.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, I think the central issue here is that President Obama's in trouble, but Bill Clinton is not.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Ari?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Two.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "David Gergen, your top takeaway?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "You know, I think he probably just broadened it out, rather than just having it Google-specific.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What's your assessment?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "In China.", "docId": "120906pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "And it's interesting he mentioned Steve Jobs -- he mentioned Steve Jobs, and most of the work that Apple does is where?", "qSentId": 354}]